gameduell.com 2015-04-30

# Privacy Protection at GameDuell

**GameDuell is committed to Your privacy**

We value Your patronage and respect Your privacy rights. As part of the normal operation of Our services, We collect and, in some cases, may disclose information about You. We have created the following Privacy Policy to let You know what information We collect when You visit Our Website, why We collect it, and how it is used. This Privacy Policy applies to all information that You provide to GameDuell, Inc. ("Us," "We," or "Our") and that We maintain electronically, whether You provide the information through Our Website located at www.gameduell.com (the "Website"), or through other means. Additionally, this Privacy Policy applies to any Personal Information (defined below) obtained from Your use of the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that You may provide to third parties; for example, other sites linked to this Website. You should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies. 

This Privacy Policy is governed by Our Terms and Conditions. GameDuell reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. In such an event, GameDuell will send You an email containing the revised terms or a notification containing a link to where the revised terms can be viewed on the Website at least two (2) weeks before they go into effect. GameDuell may also send notice of the revisions to You using the GameDuell messaging service. If You do not expressly object to the validity of the new terms and conditions via e-mail within this two (2) week period, then the newly revised Privacy Policy will be considered agreed upon. If You reject the newly revised Privacy Policy, then GameDuell may terminate its relationship with You. If You believe We have not adhered to this Privacy Policy or if You have any other questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact Us at **privacypolicy@gameduell.com**.

### 1\. Special note about children

This Website is targeted primarily for use by adults. We do not currently market to or create special areas for use by children. Accordingly, We do not knowingly collect age identifying information, nor do We knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 years. However, We hereby advise all visitors to Our site under the age of 13 not to disclose or provide any Personal Information on Our Website. In the event that We discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to Us, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (please see the Federal Trade Commission's Website at www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy for more information about this Act), We will delete the child's Personal Information from Our files to the extent technologically possible.

### 2\. What personal information do we collect from You and why?

We collect and maintain a variety of Personal Information about You to enable Us to provide You with the best service. "Personal Information" is information about You by which You may be identified. We currently collect Personal Information through e-mail and the various online inquiry forms on the Website. The Personal Information We collect and maintain about You includes: 

  * Your name, Your phone number (mobile and/or home), address (street and e-mail), date of birth, and ID or passport number (when applicable), and gender; and 

  * Your bank information (when applicable).

We only collect Personal Information that You voluntarily provide to Us or voluntarily provide to Our Partners (defined below) who share that information with Us. We also use Your Personal Information for other things that may include, but are not limited to, the following: 

  * Contacting You  
We use Your Personal Information to communicate with You in the event We have any questions with regard to any online inquiry You may have or if, in accord with Our Terms and Conditions, We need to contact you. We may also contact You to tell You about products and services provided by Our Partners, other affiliates, and other third party organizations.

  * Interactions  
Each time You interact with Our Website, the details of Your interaction are collected and retained by Us.

  * Correspondence  
We intend to retain any correspondence, including facsimiles, mail and e-mails, set to Us. We also may retain correspondence such as customer service e-mails from Us to You, and photocopy of Your ID or Passport (when applicable). We may delete such records over time.

  * Use of IP Address  
IP addresses are numbers that are automatically assigned to Your computer, and, if associated with other individually identifiable information, could be considered personal information. Your user IP address information is used only for Our internal tracking and marketing purposes.

  * Use of Cookies  
In order for Us to provide You with the best possible service on Our Website, Your browser must accept cookies, as they are essential for site administration and security. We do not use cookies either to collect individually identifiable information or to collect non-individually identifiable information using a cookie that is combined with a personal identifier. 

  * Google Analytics 

In order to provide the best possible service for our users, we use "cookies" which enable us to analyse user behaviour. We currently use the tracking and analysis technology from "Google Analytics."

The analysis is conducted **partially anonymously** so that exact conclusions about you as a user are not possible. The data is only temporarily saved for the period of analysis. It is permanently deleted afterwards.

The compiled data cannot be used to personally identify users of our website. The data is exclusively used for the purpose of optimising our offer. An additional use or transmission of the data to a third party does not occur at any time.

Through the use of this website you have declared yourself in agreement with the use of data collected from you in the manner described above and for the previously mentioned purpose. You can, of course, revoke this anonymous analysis of your surfing behaviour at any time by sending a mail to **revoke-consent@gameduell.com**.

Details Concerning the Use of Google Analytics:

GameDuell employs "Google Analytics" from Google Inc. ("Google") for the analysis of site usage. This service makes use of “cookies,” or small text files that are saved onto your computer in order to enable this analysis. The information about your use of this website generated through the cookie is transmitted to a Google server in the USA and saved there.

Anonymisation: We advise you that the "Google Analytics" code "gat._anonymizeIp();" has been enabled on this website in order to ensure an anonymised record of IP addresses (so-called IP masking). 

Google uses this information on our behalf to evaluate the use of the website, compile reports, and to ascertain related services in connection with website and internet usage of the site's users.

The IP address transmitted from your browser within the framework of "Google Analytics" is not consolidated with other data from Google. You can prevent the saving of cookies through a corresponding configuration of your browser software. However, we advise you that by doing so you may not be able to make full use of various functions of this website.

In addition, you can prevent the compilation generated by the cookie, and the use of your site-related data (including your IP address) by Google, as well as the processing of this data by Google, by downloading and installing the following browser plugin contained in this [link](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-US).

You can find more information [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-US) and [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) (general information regarding "Google" Analytics and data protection).

  * Details of Webtrekk GmbH services:

Using services provided by Webtrekk GmbH, Hannoversche Str. 19, 10115 Berlin, we can collect and use data relating to the usage of our website. This helps us improve our products and services. When you use the website, information sent by your browser is collected and analyzed. This is done by means of the cookie technology and pixels tags that are integrated into every website. 

Data collected in this way are used to generate **anonymous user profiles without identifiers**. These form the basis for our web statistics. 

You can **block** collection and use of data by Webtrekk GmbH at any time by clicking [here](http://www.webtrekk.com/en/index/dataprivacy/cookieoptout.html). Clicking on this link will set an opt-out cookie on your data carrier which is valid for 5 years. Please note that if you clear all cookies from your computer this opt-out cookie will also be deleted. This means that you will need to replace the opt-out cookie if you wish to continue to refuse anonymous data collection by Webtrekk. 

The opt-out cookie must be set separately on each browser and computer. If you visit our website using several computers or different browsers you will need to activate the opt-out cookie on each of those browsers and computers.

  * "Social Plugins" are used to improve the customization of our offer for each respective user.

First of all, we offer an additional, alternative method of registration and login via Facebook Connect. This option is provided by Facebook, Inc.

When using Facebook Connect, the data (e.g., User ID, email address registered with Facebook, some details shared with 'everyone') from your Facebook profile is transferred to our website. Similarly, the data provided on our website may be communicated to your Facebook profile. The data imported from your Facebook profile may be stored and processed by us.

The use of Facebook Connect is subject to the terms and conditions of the Data Use Policy on the Facebook platform. You can find more information about the protection of data on Facebook here: <http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>

In the event that you do not agree with these data sharing conditions, we advise you not to login with Facebook Connect. If you have already activated Facebook Connect, you can always disable it at any time by unsubscribing through our website as follows:

My GameDuell > Facebook Login > Disconnect

We will update the Terms & Conditions when there are further developments or any additional "Social Plugins" are available.

### 3\. What general information do we collect from You and why?

"General Information" is information about You or Your activities on Our Website that do not identify You personally. When You use the Internet, Your Web browser or software may communicate certain information to the host Website You visit. This information may include the unique number assigned to Your server or Internet connection, the capabilities and features of Your computer, You geographic location, and Your movement and activity within a particular Website. We collect the same information on Our Website. We use this General Information to generate statistics about visitors to Our Website.

### 4\. How we use Your information

The information We collect is used to (i) to respond to Your inquiries; (ii) provide customer services and resolve any complaints; (iii) improve the Website and service and resolve any technical problems; (iv) communicate with You concerning the services offered on the Website by Us or any of Our Partners; (v) cross-reference with other Personal Information that We have acquired about You or may acquire about You through other sources; (vi) create aggregate data; (vii) ensure compliance with the Website Terms of use; and (viii) comply with any applicable laws and regulations. We may provide Your information to government officials and agencies as required by law, and Partners as part of business operations, transaction processing, and marketing efforts, as identified below. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Partner" shall mean any person or entity with whom We enter into any kind of business transaction who is under an obligation to Us to use reasonable care to keep Personal Information confidential.

### 5\. Disclosure of information we collect

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, We will not sell, trade, or disclose to third parties any Personal Information obtained by Us through this Website or from Our Partners about You, without Your consent. We may disclose Personal Information (i) to companies that help process the transactions You request, in order to protect Your transactions from fraud and verify Your identity; (ii) that We in good faith believe is necessary or appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud, intellectual property infringements or other activity that is illegal or may expose Us or You to legal liability, or to conduct investigations of violations of the Website Terms of use; (iii) when required by law or to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (iv) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of governmental authorities (including, without limitation, requests from the governmental agency authorities to view Your Personal Information); (v) to protect and defend Us, Our subsidiaries and affiliates and any of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors and partners, in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; (vi) to prevent imminent physical harm; (vii) to share aggregated statistical or demographic data with Our affiliates, business partners or for public relations (this aggregated information is not tied to Personal Information); (viii) to provide data, including Personal Information about You, with Our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries and Partners; (ix) to sell or otherwise provide to third parties in the event of a bankruptcy or liquidation; and (x) to sell or otherwise provide to third parties in the event of a future merge or acquisition by another company. In the event We merge or are acquired by another company, the successor company will have access to Your Personal Information in order to continue to provide services, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy unless and until it is amended as described in the subsection labeled "Changes to this Privacy Policy" below.

### 6\. How we protect information we collect

We offer secure Web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and We store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on Our system. Although no computer system is completely secure, We believe the measures implemented on Our Website reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

### 7\. How long we keep user information

We generally keep user data on Our server or in Our archives for as long as We reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, We may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely. 

Data management requests are administered in an orderly manner to the extent feasible and within Our direct control. Please note that We have greater control over recently collected data than over archived data. Once data is removed from the system and archived, it may not be feasible to accommodate specific requests. In those cases, Our general data retention policy applies.

### 8\. Personal choice in the disclosure of Your information

If You do not want Us to share Your Personal Information with Our Partners for marketing purposes, or if You do not want to receive certain communications and offers from Us You can "opt out" of such sharing, communications and offers by calling Us at +49 (0)30 288 768 246 or email Us at **privacypolicy@gameduell.com** , or write Us at: 

GameDuell INC 

207 Powell St., Ste. 200 

San Francisco CA 94102

### 9\. Changes to this privacy policy

By Using this Website, You agree to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. When this Privacy Policy is changed, modified or amended, the revised Privacy Policy will be posted on this Website as identified above. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Personal Information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy.

### 10\. If You have a privacy question

If You have a privacy question about this Website, please email: 

Customer Service at **service@gameduell.com**

Or write to:  
GameDuell INC  
703 Market St., Ste. 350  
San Francisco CA 94110 

**Date Last Modified: July 04, 2013.**
